

zubairbabar@live.com

+92-300-0458-432

🙎 Lahore-Pakistan

#### **EDUCATION**

- University of Management and Technology - UMT
   Master of Supply Chain Management
- Virtual University of Pakistan
   Associate Degree in Supply Chain
- Pakistan Institute of Management
   Diploma in Procurement and Supply
   Chain Management

#### SKILL

- Management Skills
- Vendor Management
- Negotiation
- Critical Thinking
- Communication Skills
- · Problem Solving

# Zubair Babar Supply Chain Profesional

#### **PROFILE**

Experienced Supply Chain Manager with a demonstrated history of working in different industries. Skilled in Negotiation, Operations Management, Textile Industry, Textiles, and Team Building. Strong purchasing professional with a Degree focused in Supply Chain Management from University of Management & Technology.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Nishat Mills Ltd | Manager Materials & Planning Mar 2023 - Present

Oversees the efficient management of materials and inventory, coordinating planning strategies to optimize supply chain operations and meet production demands.

#### US Apparel & Textiles | Procurement Manager Jan 2022 - Mar 2023

Responsible for sourcing, negotiating, and purchasing goods and services, ensuring cost-effective procurement strategies and maintaining strong supplier relationships.

## Leathertex Group | Supply Chain Manager Mar 2021 – Jan 2022

Oversees end-to-end supply chain operations, including procurement, logistics, inventory management, and distribution, to ensure streamlined processes and efficient delivery of products or services.

## Sapphire Finishing Mills Ltd. | Dy. Manager Procurement Jan 2012 – Mar 2021

Assists the Procurement Manager in sourcing, purchasing, and supplier management, contributing to the development and implementation of effective procurement strategies and processes.

### Nishat Chunian Power Ltd. | Store Officer Mar 2011 – Jan 2012

Southern Electric Power Company Ltd. | Operations Officer Mar 2010 – Mar 2011

Kohinoor Mills Ltd. | Warehouse Supervisor May 2006 – Mar 2010

# REFERENCES Sajid Mehmood

Nizam Canvas / CEO

Yasin M. Khan

Sapphire Finishing Mills Ltd. / GM

**Phone:** 0300-4016772 **Phone:** 03004009734

Email: mehmoodsajid@hotmail.com Email: yasinmkhan@gmail.com